<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mvp short stories</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">Splash</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mystery">Mystery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_horror">Horror</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fiction">Fiction</string>
    <string name='m_text'>
        One day\,quietly opened the front door without
saying anything and stood beneath
the shadow of the banyan tree as I
was waiting for the mysterious \"Kabuliwala"\.
suddenly, he appeared in front of me;
that day, he was looking very much pale,
he was crying! I came gently near him and
tried to wipe off his tears from his eyes
with my gentle hand and asked, \"Are you
crying?\"
"Yes, my dear! I have to leave this city,
somebody has cheated me! He has borrowed
some money and dry fruits from me and
now he is denying to return them back, I have
beaten him; now, some people are chasing
me (may be police!)." His voice was full
of agony, then he put his hand into his
pouch and pulled out something for me,
this time, there was no dry fruit within
his hand, he gave me a garland made
of some glittering materials, as I stretched
it, I found lots of stars along with the sun
and moon were designed on it! Earlier, some
of my dreams were slipped out from my
tongue near him and that was to capture
the moon, sun and stars in my hand!
As I just started to concentrate on it,
the man disappeared from my sight!
I ran towards the edge of the fence,
there were very small holes where
I could at least put my eyes to look
outside but I could not find him.
I searched for him by entering my head
inside some extent of the big hole
of the banyan tree as I thought, the
man might be a magician and he could
hide himself anywhere in the garden!
But my efforts were fruitless, meanwhile,
I heard our maid\'s voice calling me; I
hoped, she did not notice anything
which happened in the garden just
now, but she had a little bit of doubt about
my absent minded nature which led
me to keep the front door open. Earlier,
I told my parents about the \"Kabuliwala\"
whom I used to meet in the garden
very often and both my parents,
specially my father, laughed it off
by saying, \"You think too much
about the stories that your mother
tells you every night!\" But this time
they took the matter seriously when
I showed them the metallic garland
laid down under some fallen dry leaves
which the strange man gave into my
hands, the garland was looking very
much old and out of date but I could
remember, a few moments before when
it was given to my hand, it was shining!
My father wanted to know every thing
which I experienced about the mysterious
man and I told him everything. My mother
became very much afraid, by that time,
a panic was very much common in the
minds of many parents concerning \"Chele-
dhora\" which meant a type of kidnapper
who used to steal or take away kids or
little children in order to sell them else
where or in return, they used to demand
a huge amount of money. My mother
thought that it might be a trap of
any wicked man in order to make his
control over me so that he could
hypnotise me and steal me away. Some
neighbours suggested my parents
to take me to a doctor in order to
judge my psychological status!
A good doctor checked me and
suggested my parents, \"Don't make
her too fond of story characters,
it may effect upon her mind and
soul.\" Whatever their comments might
be I had a strong belief that the
person was real to me and it was
not my assumption. After all, my parents
decided to vacate the quarter in order
to live in a separate house as soon
as possible, but they did not need it
as within some days, my father received
a transfer order from railway department
and very soon, we were transferred to
Calcutta. After 15 years, I came again
in Asansol in order to attend a marriage
and I did not forget to visit the quarter
where we used to stay. another family
was staying there and I did not want
to disturb them. So without knocking
their door, I widened my view towards
the garden, generally, from outside, it
was not possible from any body to
look inside the garden for its long fence
around it but I noticed, one back portion
of the fence was broken and I could
not avoid myself from looking inside
the garden; the garden was full of shrubs
and wild plants, some old plants still came
into my notice, among them, the banyan
tree was looking very much old, its many
branches were bent down and some were
broken. At our time, a gardener used to
clean the garden at least once in a week,
but after 15 years, I was feeling very
much sorry for its distressed condition, probably,
the present family had hardly any time to
look after the garden! It was the solitary
afternoon and I tried to recall all my early
childhood memories, specially that strange
man\'s look was still present in my mind.
It was the same time in the afternoon
when he used to appear in front of the
window of my bedroom, but after 15
years, there was nobody present in that
garden to offer me again some delicious
dry fruits. Whoever he might be, my
imagination, or any paranormal character
or any real person, I never forgot the
taste of the dry fruits brought by
him!\"
    </string>
    <string name="h_text"></string>

</resources>
